I couldn't find anything
about Bea's father.
Thank you for taking the time
to look for Bea's father.
And don't worry.
I already have a plan for Bea and Caloy.
- So? How does it look?
- [CHARM] Wow, it's so pretty!
- It's so pretty, right?
- Definitely worth 30 million!
Keep your eyes on it later, okay?
We can't afford to lose it.
You know, guys,
I think we should get some coffee.
The event isn't until later.
[MARJ] What about the necklace?
[BILLY] I got it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We hit the jackpot with this!
But more importantly,
this will be a huge blow to Billy!
Okay.
Just tell me when and where.
I'll do anything for you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN, CALOY GRUNTING]
- Dude!
- Get off me!
- [PEPPER SPRAY HISSES]
- [SCREAMS]
Jordan! The necklace!
- Go, go, go!
- Run!
- [CALOY] Get back here!
- Go!
I'll kill both of you!
- Jordan, let's go!
- Give me the necklace!
- [CALOY GRUNTS]
- [JORDAN] Stay back. Dude.
Give me back the necklace,
or I'll kill you.
- [CALOY GROANS]
- Hands in the air!
No sudden movements!
Cuff him!
Don't make any sudden movements.
Ms. Beatrice Mercado?
You need to come with us
to the police station now.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TALIA] Well, your plan worked.
Because of you, Ms. Talia.
[TALIA] I am not considering
Bea Mercado for the position,
especially with her track record.
- Mm-hmm.
- But…
when I found out that her
case is involved with you,
I called you.
I'm worried about you, Billy.
Thank you, Ms. Talia.
She says the accusations
against her are not true.
- Mm.
- So…
I wanted to get your side of the story.
There's only one thing
you need to know, Ms. Talia.
You can't trust Bea Mercado.
And I can prove that.
How?
I'll be needing your help.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Ever since we rolled out this campaign,
there has been an increase in
the number of our followers.
And of course, this translates into
sales!
So we are continuing this campaign
with our next partner,
Billy Cariño of LoveList.
She is the perfect next partner for us.
More than just having a big following
and being a businesswoman,
she is relevant.
[BEA] We hit the jackpot with this!
But more importantly,
this will be a huge blow to Billy!
Good thing she took the bait.
Thank you.
Billy, anything for you.
In fact, I should be the one to thank you.
You know that I almost gave up on love.
I thought it was too late
for me to find someone.
If not for LoveList and you,
maybe I would not have found my forever.
So…
thank you very much.
I have to go.
Happy anniversary, my love.
[GASPS] They're beautiful.
Of course.
Thank you.
Okay.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
I can't believe she didn't involve us
in the plan.
We missed the exciting part.
I get it.
It would have been risky
if she'd told us the plan, right?
What if we'd all been nervous
and the plan had failed?
It's a good thing he was caught.
But still, it's a shame, isn't it?
I mean, imagine the suspense
and the contents we could have
made out of it, right?
♪ Even in the silence ♪
♪ You're the only one ♪
- [MOUTHS SILENTLY] She's not here yet.
- ♪ On my mind ♪
♪ Can we take a rest? ♪
♪ I might say something I'll regret ♪
♪ Baby, I won't be long ♪
♪ You matter more to me than being right ♪
♪ I'll be back by the end of the song ♪
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Even in the silence ♪
♪ You're the only one
On my mind ♪
♪ Even in the silence ♪
♪ You're the only one
On my mind ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ I won't be long ♪
♪ I'll be back by the end of the song ♪
- [UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
Our next awardee is not just
the CEO of LoveList,
but the heart behind its success.
Please join me as we celebrate
one of today's
Young Entrepreneurial awardees,
the visionary who leads
with brilliance and heart,
Ms. Benilda Cariño.
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOG]
Good evening.
A few years ago,
my friends and I were just talking
about love, heartbreak,
and finding the courage to start again.
And from those honest
late-night conversations,
LoveList was born.
Only my name is written here,
but LoveList was never built alone.
LoveList stands where it is today
because of my team,
my best friend,
my LoveList family,
and my family.
They believed in our vision,
long before there was any proof
that it would work.
So, to our partners,
thank you for helping us
create a safe space
for online dating.
And to our LoveListers,
thank you so much for entrusting
your hearts to us.
I promise, from here on,
it only gets better.
Because every Filipina
deserves to feel safe
and empowered in love.
Again, thank you very much.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
- [DOOR OPENING]
- [OFFICER] Get in.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
'Bi, you know what?
What a waste.
I had the jewelry already.
We could've been rich, my love.
And you could've gotten
your revenge on Billy.
Isn't that what you want?
I don't care about Billy.
All right?
Leave me alone.
"My love, my love."
I don't care about that Billy.
And most importantly,
I don't care about you.
[CALOY EXHALES SOFTLY]
'Bi, don't say that.
Don't touch me.
Please.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please, just leave me alone.
Okay?
Please.
Do you know I'm getting
in trouble because of you?
Because of what you've been doing.
Because you refuse to leave me alone.
So please, okay? Just leave me alone.
Because they think
we're accomplices.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I could even go to jail because of you.
So please, I'm begging you.
Please, please. Stay away from me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALOY LAUGHING]
Accomplices?! You got that right!
We're accomplices!
Accomplices in love, right?
That's how we do it.
'Bi, you know I'm right.
You love me. I know you do.
'Bi, come on.
That's how we do it…
- Crazy! You're crazy!
- [CALOY] That's how, right?
- No!
- [BEA] See, ma'am? He's crazy!
What do you mean, "crazy?!"
I'm not crazy, 'Bi!
- What I'm saying is true.
- [BEA] We only met once!
It was just karaoke! Just one duet!
And now you're harassing me?
I'm going to get arrested because of you?!
'Bi, what do you mean, harassing you?
What I feel is real. You know that, 'Bi.
You love me. I know you do!
- I'm right, aren't I?
- [BEA] I don't--
What do you mean, "love?!"
How can I love you?! We only met once!
Why do we even have to know each other
when it's true that we love each other?
'Bi, I love you!
- [BEA] Please.
- You know, when I get out--
When I escape, we'll be together.
We'll get rich, 'Bi.
We'll become rich, 'Bi.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CALOY] 'Bi, I love you!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[BILLY] Girls, congrats!
- [CHARM] Congrats!
- [BILLY] Congrats, everyone!
[TONI] Congrats! Kiss. Mwah!
- [TONI] Deserved!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you. Thank you!
- [VALERIE] Congrats.
[MARJ] Chief.
- Wow.
- [MARJ] Let's drink.
Cheers?
- [MARJ] Cheers to our chief!
- [ALL CHEERING]
- [CHARM] Whoo!
- [TONI] You were so good!
[BILLY] That also goes for you.
Billy, give me a soundbite for my vlog.
After LoveLine,
Happily Ever After, and now this award,
what's next for the Billy Cariño
and LoveList?
Wow, what's next?
Well, I'm always reading
the comments about us,
and I noticed our supporters aren't
just here in the Philippines.
We're also being noticed
in other countries.
So, what if
we offer LoveList for global franchising?
- [TONI] Ooh!
- [CHARM] Oh, I like that!
I like that, I love it!
Universe, let's manifest it!
- [MARJ] Yes, let's get it!
- [CHARM, TONI GIGGLING]
- Congratulations, girls.
- [CHARM] Congrats, girls!
- Congrats! Cheers!
- Cheers!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, sure.
[INDISTINCT SOCIAL CHATTER]
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Congratulations!
- Thank you! Good night!
Dude, congrats!
Thank you!
For the award and for Caloy's arrest.
- Oh, yes.
- As we speak,
I believe Bea has already been
taken to the police station.
- Mm.
- Thank God!
Oh! You can use my room, okay?
Once I take off my makeup,
I'm heading home, so it's yours.
No, it's okay.
- Why?
- Come on, let's celebrate.
Let's go!
Ma'am, you see?
I had nothing to do with him!
[BEA WHIMPERS]
He's totally out of his mind.
He's obsessed with me.
For him to say everything he did
was for me?!
Is that really so?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, it was for me!
It was for me,
but I never told him to do anything!
I never asked him to do anything
because I don't even know him!
Ma'am, please. I'm innocent.
Don't lock me up!
Please, I'm begging you.
Ma'am, I don't want to go to jail.
I don't want to go to jail!
Please believe me.
Ma'am, I don't know him.
I had nothing to do with this.
I never told him to do anything. Please!
Dude, cheers to you
and to your genius plan.
Genius!
Congrats to us!
- Thank you.
- [JORDAN] And now…
Caloy's behind bars.
One problem solved.
Cheers.
And cheers to your acting too.
Because you're the best actor.
You really nailed it earlier.
Of course. You know how talented I am.
Mm! You really are!
Did you see earlier?
After your performance,
so many women came up to you.
They were handing you their calling cards.
I don't know if those were offers
for gigs or dates.
Which were they?
Both. Duh!
Wow, you really are so talented!
- Cheers to that.
- [GLASSES CLINK]
[BILLY CHUCKLES]
[WOMAN SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
Oh, it's your turn. Do you want to--
You should perform.
- Let's both do it.
- They're done.
Wanna do it?
Thank you.
[CROWD CLAPPING]
[SLOW MUSIC PLAYING IN SPEAKERS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES, FADES]
I'm sure your sister
will like Sir Eric too.
I think you and Sir Eric
make a better couple
than you and Coach Brandon.
What are you talking about?
You're too young to be thinking
about things like that.
It's way past your 10-day deadline
with Boss Zandro.
I'll pay in full
next month.
[THUG] You think I was just
bluffing with my threat?
[NURSE] You're listed as
an emergency contact.
Emergency contact for whom?
For patient Enrico Dominguez.
Your father owes my boss.
It's his debt, not mine.
- That's your problem.
- Jordan!
My friend has nothing
to do with it, okay?
Gosh, what would I do
if I didn't have
my ridiculously cocky best friend?
All he's missing
is a girlfriend.
We'll find one for him.
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]